Right now; this is the time now to strengthen your relationship with Jesus.
You have listened to the message today, that message is for you and for me.
In the church we have two Christs
The Christ - of history and story and song; the baby Jesus
Then, there is this Christ which the Holy Spirit reveals to us.
Which one are you following?
You can not know Jesus without the help of Holy Ghost.
Worshiping Jesus without the help of Holy Ghost is worshiping God you do not know.
You can read your New Testament, over and over and over and still never find Jesus in it.
You can be convinced that He is the son of God and still not find Jesus.
You can know about Jesus Christ dying for you and still never know Jesus.
You can be a publisher of the bible and still never know Jesus.
Where is Jesus? Jesus is in the power of Holy Ghost.
If you have learnt to worship one Man; you will not worship other men.Tell you neighbor
If you have learnt to worship one Man; you will not worship other men (again)
Take your pen and write it down.
If you have learnt to worship one Man; you will not worship other men.
Because you don't know Jesus that is why you can run to spiritualist.
You can run to this. You can run to spiritualist.
You can run to that. You keep running, you keep running. You keep finding God.You keep finding God.
Because you have not learnt to worship one Man.
If you have learnt to worship one Man; you will not worship other men.
I love the Man of Galilee. For He has done so very much for me.
He has forgiven me all my sins and send the Holy Ghost to me.
I love that Man of Galilee.
The most dangerous one is that if you are not filled with the Spirit of God;
you can not obey the written Word. So then.. what is your business with the Bible?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbor; the most dangerous - if you are not filled with the Spirit of God,
there is no way you can obey the written Word!
If you can not obey the written Word, you quench Him.
So what is your business with the Bible then, when you are not filled with the Spirit
when you are carrying it? Carry it, to cause confusions all over. You say this one is no good.
That religion is not good, that one is not good.That is the confusion we are having all over the world today.
Accusing this accusing that, other religion, shouting this and that. Is that what we are taught?
If you are not filled with the Spirit of God, you can not obey this Bible.
And if you can not obey this Bible; you quench Him.
So what is your business with the Bible? I am Christian, you see everyone with the Bible.
Everyone with the Cross. Big big Bible. Laptop not...there is no Bible now, it's laptop.
Everyone is having. The Bible they are supposed to is inside the laptops.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Tell your neighbour - If you are not filled with the Spirit of God; you can not obey the written Word.
And if you can not obey the written Word; you quench Him.
If your faith is to be a New Testament ; if Jesus is to be the Christ of God.
Rather than the Christ of history, and stories, then the illumination of Holy Spirit
will tell your heart that you are worshiping Him. You are learning at His feet.
So right now the business of the day; talk to yourself your heart keep your heart busy.
Begin to meditate right now. Meditate in his Word. Hymn in your heart,
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hymn in your heart. Spiritual song. Keep your heart busy with songs of praise.
I will praise Him. I will praise Him. I will praise him forever more.
Keep your heart busy with this. Soon you will be filled.
I will praise Him. Keep your heart busy. Keep your heart busy. I will praise you for ever more.
In my situation; I will praise Him. I will praise Him. I will praise Him for ever more.
In my affliction; I will praise Him. I will praise Him. I will praise Him for ever more.
Your affliction is not to kill you, it's not to kill you but to strengthen your desire and your determination for God.
That's all. That is the purpose of that.Once you start praising Him;
your affliction is not to kill you but to strengthen your desire and your determination for God.
In my situation;
So, keep your heart busy with this all the time.
A break in faith is a break in prayer and a break in prayer is a break with God. Tell your neighbor.
A break in faith is a break in prayer and a break in prayer is a break with God.
So when you have a break in your heart; when you stop meditating or praising God, satan comes.
Your heart, continue right now. Are you doing that now in your heart?
I will praise Him. I will praise Him. When you are eating, when you are ...
Soon you will be filled by the Spirit. That is how to invite the Spirit of God.
Our heart is , is in a strong conflict. There is a conflict between the flesh and Spirit.
Go, don't go; come don't come. That is what is going on in our hearts.
Our heart is busy. There is a conflict. Strong...I mean
There is a division in our hearts. Until this is out; landlord will take over.
Jesus is not a tenant. He is not a tenant. He is the Landlord He is the owner of your heart.
But your heart is divided now. There is for; there is against in your heart.
So unless this is cleared, then you invite the Holy Ghost.
Our heart is the contact point. The communication point. So start with this.
I will praise Him. I will ....Continue , your heart should continue this. Continue this.
By the time you continue this, it's not for you to choose the prayer to offer.
The heart will switch into prayer, will switch into speaking in tongues. You just hear a prayer in your heart.
Just hearing. It's not just for you to choose a prayer, just praise Him.
We are created to praise God. You are created to praise God. Your heart to praise God.
Your heart, your heart, your heart, your heart, your heart. Thank you Lord.Thank you Lord.
So this the prayer for you now. The prayer you have been offering
Jesus do this for me, Jesus.... hour of prayer; that can not work for you.
Because you are not strong, you are a baby when it come to things of the spirit, you a baby.
You need to build your foundation is first.
Your foundation is to keep your heart busy with praising.
You are still crawling. You are a baby, just a baby. You can not offer prayer here now.
because whom are you praying to God you do not know.
Do you know God? You don't know God and you are praying. How can you pray to God you do not know?
Until you know God before you pray; If you don't know your father can you ask your father things?
You need to know your father before you pray, before you ask your father.
But here now; you don't know your father because there is no Holy Spirit.
Tell your neighbour - you need to know God before prayer.
But if you don't know God and you are praying, whom are you praying to.
So foundation first. Get your heart to your side. Your heart is not on your side.
It's like your heart is somewhere When you are looking at me, your heart will say
mmm can T.B. Joshua do it? hmm look at what is happening aah ooh. Time is going.
This man should finish quick. Aah someone is waiting for me.
Your heart keep jumping jumping. Your heart is not on your side.
Until you get your heart to your side then Holy Spirit comes in.
Tell your neighbour - get your heart to your side
So now your heart; I will praise Him. I will praise Him. I will praise Him for ever more.
All the time, all the time , let this one run, let this one keep running, keep running in your heart all the time,
all day long. Even when you are sleeping till you sleep off.
This is why we give you faith bracelet to help on the outside.
Build the foundation before prayer. Know the father before prayer.
You don't know God and you are praying to God.
How can you pray to God you do not know? If you know Him , He will answer you.
But this time you pray; no answer because you don't know him.
Someone keep telling you , this is your God, Jesus is your God. But you are trying to know God
In what way without the Holy Ghost.
When you know your God, He will tell you pray this time, meet me this time, appointment this time.
God relates to all like a father. He relate to all. Like I am talking now if I hear it's alright
I will just say the Grace and leave here. Tell your neighbour -
You need to know God before prayer. If you don't know God; who are you praying to ?
This is the time for foundation. Get your heart to your side; Holy Spirit will come in.
Thank you Lord, thank you Lord, thank you Lord. This is a special Grace. It's a Grace
And the Word given to you today, be a hearer in the name of Jesus. (Amen)
Be a hearer in the name of Jesus! (Amen)
Right now open your lips and confess whom you are. Whom you are now.
I am what God say I am! I can do what God say I can do!
I have what God say I have. Confess it, that is the platform now
I am what God say I am!
I can do what God say I can do.
I am what God say I am! In Jesus Christ's name! (Amen)
Can someone tell me , "What is your problem now? You should be able to tell me.
All these challenges, sickness. Sickness is not a problem. Setback is not a problem.
Stagnation is not a problem. The problem is; we don't know God who we are praying to.
If you know me , you talk to me I will answer you. If I can not tell you, I will tell you hold on.
But this is absent. When we pray , we don't hear from God.
In the name of Jesus, do it for me , do it for me. Why can't you wait and let God reply?
We pray and say Amen. So it's two sides - you talk; God talks. You talk, God talks.
That is God, real God. He talks. God talks. If you are my father - How are you Sir?
I am doing fine - How are you doing? - I am ok. That is God
But in this case today; oh my God, we are the only person who is talking.
We never hear from Father, Jesus.
Open your lips; Make us a channel of faithfulness, a channel of shining light.
Make us your channel of love. Make us your channel of pardon.
Make us your channel of forgiveness where there is sin.
Make us your channel of faithfulness, In Jesus Christ's name.
You are a channel of God. As you are going now, anywhere you are, you are a channel.
He has no mouth but your mouth to talk. He has no hands, your hands. He has no feet.
Say I am a channel of God - channel of love, pardon, forgiveness, faithfulness, obedience. In Jesus Christ's name. Amen.
TT Monica Asefa 16/10/18